Guide to the Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015.
Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015
- Series I. Administrative Files
  - Executive Staff
    - Elizabeth Birch, 1994-2004
      - National Black Gay and Lesbian Leadership Forum, 1994-2000 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - NLGTF, 1994-2000 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Transgender, 1994-2000 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - HRC Foundation and the HRC Fund, 1995-2000 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - John L. Sullivan, 1995-2000 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Philadelphia Inquirer, 1995-2000 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - Strategic Plan '98, 1996-1998 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - Colorado Trips, 1996-1999 (Box 118, Folder 10)
      - Columbus, 1996-1999 (Box 118, Folder 11)
      - George Magazine, 1996-1999 (Box 118, Folder 12)
      - IBM, 1996-1999 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      - National Organization of Women (Patricia Ireland), 1996-1999 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      - Tennessee Political Memos, 1996-1999 (Box 118, Folder 15)
      - Whitman-Walker, 1996-1999 (Box 118, Folder 16)
      - Artists- NO, 1996-2000 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      - P-FLAG, 1996-2000 (Box 118, Folder 18)
      - Dallas Contacts, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 19)
      - Dallas, Santa Cruz, LA- 2/4-2/9, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 20)
      - GSC- Keying Questions Pending, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 21)
      - Philadelphia, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 22)
      - South Carolina, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 23)
      - Adoption, 1997-1999 (Box 118, Folder 24)
      - Aspen, 1997-1999 (Box 118, Folder 25)
      - Atlanta Contacts, 1997-1999 (Box 118, Folder 26)
      - Boston, 1997-1999 (Box 118, Folder 27)
      - Florida, 1997-1999 (Box 118, Folder 28)
      - Campaign Activities, 1997-2000 (Box 118, Folder 29)
      - General Mills, 1997-2000 (Box 118, Folder 30)
      - Arkansas, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 31)
      - Atlanta Trip- 3/19, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 32)
      - Dallas Dinner- 11/7/98, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 33)
      - HRC: Towards a Million Members, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 34)
      - Maine, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 35)
      - MN Speech 98, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 36)
      - New York Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 37)
      - NYC Fed. Club, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 38)
      - Oklahoma, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 39)
      - Philadelphia Contacts, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 40)
      - Elton John, 1998-1999 (Box 118, Folder 41)
      - Jim Hormel, 1998-1999 (Box 118, Folder 42)
      - Melissa Etheridge, 1998-1999 (Box 118, Folder 43)
      - Democratic National Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 118, Folder 44)
      - AIDS in Sub-Saharan Africa, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 45)
      - Atlanta, 4/30- 5/1, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 46)
      - Dallas Black Tie Dinner, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 47)
      - Death Penalty, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 48)
      - ER Don Was, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 49)
      - ER Print Ads, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 50)
      - ER Television, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 51)
      - Hawaii, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 52)
      - HRC Political Dept., 1999 (Box 118, Folder 53)
      - Ingrid Caseres, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 54)
      - Laurette Healey, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 55)
      - Mary Cahill, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 56)
      - Nike, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 57)
      - Planet Out, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 58)
      - President Clinton, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 59)
      - Rel Liberty Prot Act, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 60)
      - Santa Clara, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 61)
      - Seattle, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 62)
      - Stadium Seating, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 63)
      - Texas- Hate Crimes, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 64)
      - United Airlines, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 65)
      - ER Corporate, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 66)
      - ER Memos, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 67)
      - ER Message, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 68)
      - Shell- Sept. 10, 2001- Houston, 1996-2001 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      - GLAAD, 1997-2001 (Box 119, Folder 2)
      - Enda Meeting Background- Feb. 5, 1997-2002 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      - HRC Pamphlets, 1997-2002 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      - MMOW BRD Calls (1), 1998-2001 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      - MMOW BRD Calls (2), 1998-2001 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      - Oklahoma Contacts, 1998-2001 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      - ER Producers, 1999-2000 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      - Heather Quinn Letters, 1999-2000 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      - Purchase of 1640 RI Ave- Docs, 1999-2002 (Box 119, Folder 10)
      - Adoption, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      - CD ERocks, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      - Diversity, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 13)
      - Equality Rocks- Photos, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 14)
      - Equality Rocks Videocassette, 2000; V-5644 (Box 119, Folder 15)
      - ER Cancellation Ins, 2000 (Box 119, Folder 16)
      - National Dinner 2000 (Box 119, Folder 17)
      - National Dinner 2000- Urgent (Box 119, Folder 18)
      - 2 tape recordings: God Loves Us All (Sager/Feinstein) and "Question," "Family," "Al Miyasato," and "Jean Aoki", 2000; tr-8784a, tr-8785d (Box 119, Folder 19)
      - Youth College 2000 (Box 119, Folder 20)
      - Co-Chair List- Gala Dinners, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 21)
      - HRC Talking Points, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 22)
      - AT+T League- June 7, 2001- Orlando (Box 119, Folder 23)
      - Bush Era Judicial Appts, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 24)
      - Chicago/Boston- Oct 26-27, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 25)
      - Dept. of Agriculture, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 26)
      - ERocks II, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 27)
      - Events Calendar- FY02 and 03, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 28)
      - Faith-Based Initia, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 29)
      - Free State Justice Event, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 30)
      - Girl Scouts, USA, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 31)
      - Helm's Amendment, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 32)
      - Justification for Writing Regulations for Federal Victim Compensation Fund that are Inclusive of Domestic Partners (1), 2001 (Box 119, Folder 33)
      - Justification for Writing Regulations for Federal Victim Compensation Fund that are Inclusive of Domestic Partners (2), 2001 (Box 119, Folder 34)
      - Maryland, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 35)
      - Military Photo, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 36)
      - Minnesota, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 37)
      - 9/11, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 38)
      - Palm Springs- Dec. 2001 (Box 119, Folder 39)
      - Republican Outreach, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 40)
      - Research Outside, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 41)
      - SF Event and Community Event, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 42)
      - Southern Poverty Law Center, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 43)
      - Speeches, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 44)
      - Spitzer, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 45)
      - Budget 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 46)
      - Claudia French, 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 47)
      - Corporate Recognition Matrix, 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 48)
      - 9/11 Relief Efforts, 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 49)
      - NYC Relief (1), 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 50)
      - NYC Relief (2), 2001-2002 (Box 119, Folder 51)
      - EB- Contract Extension Memo to Brd, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 52)
      - EB. HR Ascroft- Re: Hate Crimes, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 53)
      - Home Depot, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 54)
      - HRCF- Community Action Program Pilot Report, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 55)
      - Mychal Judge Act, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 55)
      - Strategic Planning, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - Youth College 2002 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - Ford Sponsorship, 2002-2003 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      - HRC Pamphlets, 2002-2003 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      - Corporate Sponsor Packets, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 5)
      - FY04 Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 120, Folder 6)
      - HRC Strategic Plan, 1996-2004 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Blueprint for Bush, 2001-2004 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - Box Office Tickets Form, 2001-2004 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - HRC Marriage Plan (1), 2003-2004 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - HRC Marriage Plan (2), 2003-2004 (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - Marriage, 2003-2004 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - Project "Out There", November 11, 1999 (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - "What We Do" (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Strategic Plan 1999-2004 (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - The Five Year Strategic Plan 2005-2010, July 23, 2005 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - Board Rosters, 2002-2005 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Harvey Hurdle (Chief Operating Officer), 2001-2005 (Box 90)
    - Cheryl Jacques, 2004 (Box 91)
  - Board Materials
    Included here are the agenda, minutes, and correspondence from Board meetings, drafts of reports they produce, and other files produced by HRC's Board of Directors, Board of Governors, and the Human Rights Campaign Foundation Board. Note that most of these vital records have not yet been transferred to the archives, and their use is currently restricted. Some memoranda from the Board are found throughout the collection, in the files of various departments and units of HRC(F).
    - HRCF - Board member correspondence re: Contributions, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - HRCF - Board/Internal Correspondence, 1982/1983 (Box 79, Folder 65)
    - HRCF - Board of Directors Meeting, March 1983 (Box 79, Folder 66)
    - HRC Goals, Leadership Conference, Bi-weekly reports from Executive Director to Board of Directors, Board meetings, Budget, 1995-1997 (Box 82)
    - Board and Leadership Conference, By-laws, March 1996-1998 (Box 83)
    - Board and Budget, March 1998-2003 (Box 84)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1991-1996 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Briefing Papers, 1992-1993 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Military, May 1993 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Solomon Amendment, 1994-1997 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Morale, 1994-2000 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - E. Birch Memos and Correspondence, 1994-2003 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Phone Book- October, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Phone Book- December, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Agenda, January 28, 1984 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Board Meeting-Election Disbursement Guidelines, April 24-25, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - HRC Legal Department, 1997-2000
    - HRC Legal dept. -various, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - (LAMBDA) Lesbian & Gay Civil Rights Litigators Roundtable, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - House & Senate Gift Ban, Rule 52, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - HRC Internet Domains Registration, July 1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - HRC Legal--Lobbying Registration, 1996-98 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Gay Marriage-Vermont-Baker v. State, 1997-98 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Gay Marriage-DOMA & Gay Marriage Issues (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Gay Marriage-Hawaii, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Gay Marriage-Alaska, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Final Draft Strategic Plan with Tasks 1999-2004, Mar 1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - HRC Legal-HRC Legal Fellows-Tamara Ahmar's papers, HRC Orientation materials, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - HRC Legal-Millennium March on Washington-legal docs, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - HRC Legal-Chron Files (T. Ahmar), May 1999-December 1999 (Box 1, Folder 30-35)
    - Hawaii Ballot Initiative, 1997-98 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Gay Marriage-Comparison of State laws//Hawaii litigation, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - HRC Legal-Chron File (Cheryl Henson-paralegal), Oct 1999 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - HRC Legal dept. -various, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - HRC Legal-Chron Files (Cheryl Henson), February-December 2000 (Box 56, Folder 17-21)
    - Board of Directors & Board of Governors rosters, Mar 1999 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Reports and Operations
    Annual reports, financial reports, staff rosters and staff reports, personnel manuals, and other files from the overall operation and administration of the agency. Additional annual reports were cataloged separately in a collection titled "Miscellaneous Human Rights Campaign periodicals and newsletters."
    - HRCF Strategic Plan 1989 - 1993 (draft Sept 14, 1988) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - HRCF - Financial - FEC "Reports of Receipts & Disbursements", 7-9/30/80 and 1-6/30/1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - HRCF - Organizational Audit Report, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - HRC Personnel- Union Contract, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - HRC Personnel- Handbook- revisions, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - HRCF - Retreat info. - HRCF Retreat 1989, Program Department (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Staff/Board of Directors rosters, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - HRCF Year and Financials- Audit FY '94, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - HRC Summary Financial Ledgers, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - HRCF Foundation- year and Financial Statements, Mar. 31 1995 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - HRC Combined Operating Budgets Apr. 1996- Mar. 1997 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - HRCF Summary Audit Financial Reports, March 31, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - HRC Hawaii POC- Final prelim. Campaign Spending 9/05-19/98, prelim general campaign spending 9/20-10/18/98 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - HRC Hawaii Protect Our Constitution campaign- Primary Disclosure Report Financials (Financial report -state), 1997-98 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - HRC Accounting Policies, memos, reviews, 1994-1998 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - HRC Hawaii POC campaign- Final disclosure report (1998), 1999 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Bank Account (Part 1), 1984-1993 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Bank Account (Part 2), 1984-1993 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - IRS Documentation, July 31, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Disbursements, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Membership and Fundraising
    Included here are files from HRC(F)'s efforts to encourage membership, including files from the Insider Program, later the Federal Club, and the Sustainer Program. Much of the work to encourage new members happened at the local level at events planned by the Constituent Mobilization Division and Field office, so researchers should look in those series too. Also here is documentation of HRC's communication with its members, including member feedback on issues, both protest and support. The direct marketing files show HRC's efforts at communicating with members and appealing for funds through the years. Also included are correspondence and files from the Development Department. Records containing financial information are restricted for 25 years from date of creation.
    - Membership Programs
      - Insider Program: Operations Manual, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Insider Program: Susan Hestor Proposal to Enhance Program, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Insider Program: Dan Bradley Biography File - Obituary, Press Clippings, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Insider Program: Correspondence -Insider's Report Conference, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Insider Program: Second Annual Conference, Oct. 1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - Sustainer Program: Operations Manual, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Sustainer Program: Mailings, Examples, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Federal Club Conference, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Federal Club membership documents, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Member Feedback on Issues
      - Feedback from members re: Domestic Partnership/Adoption, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - HRC's support of Sen. D'Amato- letter to cancelled members (drafts and final), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - HRC's support of Sen. D'Amato- Feedback from members, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Logbook support of calls regarding Sen. D'Amato, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato (telemarker pledge), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato (NO NY's mailed Entire file 135,000), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence from members re: Support for Sen. D'Amato (sample letters), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence from members re: Support for Sen. D'Amato, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato (we did mail NY; prospects not current members; 300,000; January), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato (1st year end; entire "core file" no NY's mailed; 100,000) (Political; mailed October '98 to members who have given at least $20 in last 24 mos.), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
      - Feedback from members re: Sen. D'Amato (Sample Emails -through D'Amato Crisis HRC Logged over 1,000 email (this is an under estimation)), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Feedback from members re: D'Amato, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Feedback from members re: Don't Ask/Don't Tell, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Feedback from members re: Matthew Shepard, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Feedback from members re: Millennium March, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Direct Mail Examples
      - HRC Direct Mail-Address Label Prospect, Jan. 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Activist Prospect, Jan. 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - HRC Direct Mail-May Prospect HR56P1 Pkg A, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - HRC Direct Mail-March Prospect HR36P1-Control Version, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - HRC Direct Mail-V-4 dummies, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - HRC Direct Mail-March Prospects HR36P1-Sticker Test, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - HRC Direct Mail-HR96P1 Membership Prospect HRC, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - HRC Direct Mail-March Prospect-ENDA version (HR36P2), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership prospectus-free magazines, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - HRC Direct Mail-New member prospect-referral letter, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Second request: "Liberty and justice for all", 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Women's Piece, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - HRC Direct Mail-ENDA Petition, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Member get a member HRB7PP, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Public Opinion Survey/membership enrollment form, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Nohat non-union/nonrecycled, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Magazine Prospect, Sept. 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Prospect, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Proposal '99, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Proposal '99, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership form, circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Proposal, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Proposal '99, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Proposal '99, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership contribution form (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership form (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - HRC Direct Mail-First renewal, Jan. 95 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership renewal, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - HRC Direct Mail-4th renewal, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - HRC Direct Mail-1st renewal, Jan 1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - HRC Direct Mail-renewal notices, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - HRC Direct Mail-3rd renewal, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - HRC Direct Mail-5th renewal, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership Renewal, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership Renewal, Jan 1997 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership Renewal, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Prospect '99, Apr 1999 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Holiday Card, Dec.1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Candace Appeal, May 1995 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Helms PAC Appeal, July 1995 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Ryan White Urgent Gram, Sept.1995 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Maine won't discriminate appeal, Oct.1995 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Year End Appeal BRE version 3rd class HRB5A1, Nov.1995 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Years end appeal BRE Version 1st class HRB5A1, Nov. 1995 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - HRC Direct Mail-PAC appeal, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Lo$PAC Campaign HR76A1 PkgA (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Lo$PAC Campaign HR76A1 PkgB (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Seps PAC Appeal (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - HRC Direct Mail-CA Seps Appeal, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - HRC Direct Mail-105th congress-"Congrats on Victory", 1996 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - HRC Direct Mail-CA appeal HR96A3, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Membership survey-contribution form, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - HRC Direct Mail-, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - HRC Direct Mail-LO$PAC appeal HR76A1 (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Hi$PAC Appeal 5196 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - HRC Direct Mail-1996 welcome packets/memb. card (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - HRC Direct Mail-1996 welcome packets/memb. card (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - HRC Direct Mail-membership card, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - HRC Direct Mail-credit card pledges, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - HRC Direct Mail-pledge reminders, c. 1997 (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - HRC Direct Mail-specified pledges, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - HRC Direct Mail-ENDA appeal, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - HRC Direct Mail-member survey, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - HRC Direct Mail-survey and petition, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - HRC Direct Mail-pledge reminder, Jun. 1997 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - HRC Direct Mail-emergency telepost appeal FY99, Aug. 1998 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - HRC Direct Mail-year end appeal, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - HRC Direct Mail-year end appeal, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - HRC Direct Mail-ACK's, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - HRC Direct Mail-welcome, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - HRC Direct Mail-campaign '98 (Box 3, Folder 71)
      - HRC Direct Mail-statewide human rights organizations, Jan1999 (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Anti-Gay ADS appeal, June 99 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Ray of Light Appeal, Aug. 1999 (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Holiday Card FY'99, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Holiday Card (appeal), 1999/2000 (Box 3, Folder 76)
      - HRC Direct Mail-NonPAC Appeal, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - HRC Direct Mail-1999 PAC appeal (Box 3, Folder 78)
      - HRC Direct Mail-"Ray of Light" Appeal (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - HRC Direct Mail-PAC Appeal, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Early Bird Appeal, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Early Bird Appeal, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Phone Pledge, 999 (Box 3, Folder 83)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Protect our constitution (Box 3, Folder 84)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Non PAC Appeal (Box 3, Folder 85)
      - HRC Direct Mail-November appeal test (Box 3, Folder 86)
      - HRC Direct Mail-California Project (Box 3, Folder 87)
      - HRC Direct Mail-LO$ letters samplers (Box 3, Folder 88)
      - HRC Direct Mail-California Project (Box 3, Folder 89)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Holiday card (Box 3, Folder 90)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Telephone contribution (Box 3, Folder 91)
      - HRC Direct Mail-HRC Partners invite, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 92)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Partners Certificate, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 93)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Partners invite, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 94)
      - HRC Direct Mail-July High Dollar survey appeal HR77A1, July 1996 (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Federal Club memorandum (Box 3, Folder 96)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Federal Club one time pledge (Box 3, Folder 97)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Federal club (Box 3, Folder 98)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Federal club request (Box 3, Folder 99)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Federal club newsletter March, April 1998 (Box 3, Folder 100)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Federal club invite (Box 3, Folder 101)
      - HRC Direct Mail-Federal club: victory in Hawaii (Box 3, Folder 102)